{
    "id": "ad4b6e89d99147ac97ebaa55ae48f412",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was .............................. a frightening experience that I couldn’t even cry.",
            "description": "Use such before adjective + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ being rich and famous, she is very humble.",
            "description": "Use despite before a noun or ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We worked day and night .............................., we could not meet the deadline.",
            "description": "However does not connect two sentences. Use it after a full stop or a semicolon. ",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "however",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. her illness, she is always cheerful.",
            "description": "Either despite or in spite of is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Inspite of",
                "In spite of",
                "Despite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You must quit .................................. you have no other option.",
            "description": "For can mean because in a very formal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The doorbell rang ............................... I closed the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "as far as",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is an upright officer ................................. her brother is corrupt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I learned English ................................ I might get a better job.",
            "description": "So that indicates purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "such that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The performance was ……………………… brilliant that the applause lasted several minutes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will buy the snacks ..................................... you buy the tickets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... I was in a hurry to leave, I forgot to lock the door.",
            "description": "As shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. he wins the scholarship, he cannot go to university.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}